(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Hmm... Am I lost again?
This door looks sus.
Should I?
Or should I not?
Dahlah.
Whatever.
Dahlah saja
It's just fine
Walk it off and go
Isn't this a thing that you're used to?
Disappointed and feeling blue
When the world doesn't go the way you want it to?
Oh, oh
And maybe now is just the perfect time
to let it go and just unwind
There's no need to ask why ever again
Just let it go
The answer you've been looking for
No need to be sad about it,
just try to get through your day
Just let it go
Then maybe in the end you'll know
You got what it takes to get through the ache
and still win the day
Dahlah saja
It's just fine
Oh, dahlah saja
Oh, it's just fine
Walk it off and go
Dahlah saja
It's just fine
Oh, dahlah saja
Oh, it's just fine
Walk it off and go
What else can you do?
When your feelings are barely there
Up to a point of pure despair
When you have given it your all
but ends in vain
Just let it go
The answer you've been looking for
No need to be sad about it,
just try to get through your day
Just let it go
Then maybe in the end you'll know
You got what it takes to get through the ache
and still win the day
Then maybe in the end you'll know
You got what it takes
To get through the ache
And still win the day
You got what it takes
To get through the ache
And still win the day
Dahlah saja
Just let it go
Oh, dahlah saja
Oh, just let it go
Walk it off and go
Dahlah saja
Just let it go
Oh, dahlah saja
Oh, just let it go
Walk it off and go
ma ii ka
Well, whatever
幽閉 利口 逝く前に
Locking up the clever one before they die
ユーヘイじゃ利口に難儀ダーリン
It's a pain to get you to be obedient, darling
幽閉 ストップ 知ってないし
Don't lock me up! It's not like I knew
勘弁にしといてなんて惨忍
Give me a break, that's so cruel
人様願う欠片のアイロニ
The irony of what people wish for
だれもが願う無機質なような
Like the inorganic thing everyone wishes for
一足先に始めてたいような
Like wanting to start a step ahead
先が見えないヴァージンハッピーショー
A virgin happy show with no end in sight
YOU ARE KING YOU ARE KING
無邪気に遊ぶ 期待 期待のダーリン ダーリン
Playing innocently, expecting darling
健気に笑う 痛い 痛いの消える
Laughing bravely, the pain fades away
無様に
Unbecomingly
レフトサイド ライトサイド
Left side, right side
歯をむき出して パッパッパッ 照れくさいね
Baring teeth, pa-pa-pa, such a nuisance, right?
レフトサイド ライトサイド
Left side, right side
歯を突き出して パッパッパッ ハハ
Thrusting out teeth, pa-pa-pa, ha-ha
YOU ARE KING YOU ARE KING
Okay, that's kind of an easy trick.
So that's how this room's work, huh?
I guess this door is locked too, right?
I need to find a clue here and get out.
OPEN THIS
ONLY FOR THE WEAK ONES
What am I supposed to do with this?
Coffee? Arrow? Right?
What?
There's another box but I'm not the weak one so...
I have no idea.
Who's going to judge me anyway if I open the next clue?
I just need to get out from here and leave this weird place...
...or else I'll be late for my 3D.
Loncat, jalan, kiri.
Jump, walk, left.
Oke, ya udah sana.
Okay, go ahead then.
Oke, satu, dua, tiga, loncat, jalan, kiri.
Okay, one, two, three, jump, walk, left.
Loncat, jalan, kanan.
Jump, walk, right.
Gak apa-apa pula lompat.
It's okay to jump too.
Loncat, kiri lagi.
Jump, left again.
Loncat, gak apa-apa ini yang penting bisa aja.
Jump, it doesn't matter as long as you can do it.
Kiri kiri kiri!
Left, left, left!
I don't get it.
Oh! Kopi kanan!
Oh! Coffee right!
Ya ampun...
Oh my goodness...
Clue apaan coba...
What kind of clue is that even...
Mentari terbenam
The sun sets
Temani dalam kesendirianku
Accompanying me in my solitude
Temani aku dalam kepedihan
Accompanying me in my pain
Ini ku bertahan
Here I endure
Mentari terbenam
The sun sets
Beri semangat baru untuk jiwaku
Giving new spirit to my soul
Beri kicauan merdu untuk hidupku
Giving a melodious chirp to my life
Ini ku bertahan
Here I endure
Aku pasti bisa
I surely can
Menikmati semua dan menghadapinya
Enjoying it all and facing it
Aku yakin pasti
I'm sure, surely
Bisa
I can
Mentari terbenam
The sun sets
Beri semangat baru untuk jiwaku
Giving new spirit to my soul
Beri kicauan merdu untuk hidupku
Giving a melodious chirp to my life
Ini ku bertahan
Here I endure
Aku pasti bisa
I surely can
Menikmati semua dan menghadapinya
Enjoying it all and facing it
Aku yakin pasti
I'm sure, surely
Bisa
I can
Aku pasti bisa
I surely can
Menikmati semua dan menghadapinya
Enjoying it all and facing it
Aku yakin pasti
I'm sure, surely
Bisa
I can
Aku ingin lepaskan seluruh bebanku
I want to release all my burdens
Dan kujalani
And I live on
...hidupku dengan senyuman
...my life with a smile.
Yay! Aku pasti bisa
Yay! I can definitely do it!
Menikmati semua dan menghadapinya
Enjoying everything and facing it all.
Aku yakin pasti bisa
I'm sure I can definitely do it.
Pasti dan kujalani hidupku dengan senyuman
Definitely, and I'll live my life with a smile.
Oh... あれ? この部屋... なんか違う?
Oh... Huh? This room... is something different?
Answer honestly: What's your hobby?
え? 趣味? 寝ること。
Eh? Hobby? Sleeping.
Answer honestly: What's your other hobby?
これ、いつまで分かるの? まあいいや、寝ること。
Does this thing know if I'm lying? Whatever, sleeping.
さっきから同じ質問じゃん! 寝ること。寝るの大好き。
It's been the same question this whole time! Sleeping. I love sleeping.
冗談でしょ、これ? 同じ質問に何を答えろっていうのよ。
Is this some kind of joke? What am I supposed to answer to the same question over and over again?
もういいから、早くドア開けてくれない?
Enough already, can't you just open the door?
いや、答えない。
No, I refuse to answer.
Dahlah.
Whatever.
Answer honestly: How many steering wheels do you need if you have your own Raft?
おっ! やっと違う質問! しかも簡単! 8! 8に決まってるでしょ!!
Oh! Finally a different question and an easy one too! 8! It's obviously 8!!
広い宇宙の数ある一つ
In this vast universe of many,
青い地球の広い世界で
on this blue earth, in this wide world,
小さな恋の思いは届く
a small love's feelings reach you,
小さな島のあなたのもとへ
on this small island.
あなたと出会い時は流れる
Meeting you, time flows.
思いを込めた手紙も増える
Letters filled with feelings increase.
いつしか二人互いに響く
Someday, the two of us will resonate,
時に激しく　時に切なく
sometimes intensely, sometimes painfully.
響くは遠く　遥か彼方へ
It resonates far into the distance.
優しい歌は世界を変える
A gentle song changes the world.
ほら　あなたにとって大事な人ほど
Look, the person most important to you
すぐそばにいるの
is right by your side.
ただあなたにだけ届いてほしい
I just want this to reach only you.
響け恋の歌
Let the love song resound.
あなたは気づく 二人は歩く 暗い道でも 日々照らす月
You will realize, as we walk together, even on dark roads, the moon shines every day.
握りしめた手 離すことなく
Never letting go of your hand,
思いは強く 永遠誓う
feelings are strong, vowing eternity.
永遠の淵 きっと僕は言う
At the edge of eternity, I'll surely say
思い変わらず 同じ言葉を
the same words, with feelings unchanged.
それでも足りず 涙に変わり
Even then it's not enough, turning into tears,
喜びになり 言葉にできず
becoming joy, unable to put into words...
ただ抱きしめる ただ抱きしめる
I just hold you close, just hold you close.
ほら　あなたにとって大事な人ほど
Look, the person most important to you
すぐそばにいるの
is right by your side.
ただあなたにだけ届いてほしい
I just want this to reach only you.
響け恋의歌
Let the love song resound.
夢ならば覚めないで
If it's a dream, don't wake up.
あなたと過ごした時
The time I spent with you...
永遠の星となる
will become an eternal star.
ほら　あなたにとって大事な人ほど
Look, the person most important to you
すぐそばにいるの
is right by your side.
響け恋の歌
Let the love song resound.
届けたい　響け　恋の歌
I want to reach you, resonate, song of love
ほら　あなたにとって
Look, for you
大事な人の　すぐそばにいるの
I'm right by the side of someone precious to you
ただ　あなたにだけ
Only for you
届いてほしい
I want it to reach
響け　恋の歌
Resonate, song of love
ほら
Look
響け　恋の歌
Resonate, song of love
REPEAT AFTER ME 10 TIMES
Eh? Ngulang apaan?
Eh? Repeat what?
Chaos?
Kepalaku memang lagi chaos sih, tapi maksudnya?
My head is indeed in chaos, but what do you mean?
Meja murid ada 5, terus ada meja guru satu.
5 student tables, then one teacher table.
Aku nggak paham.
I don't understand.
Hmm... chaos.
Eh?
Hakos Baelz?
Jangan-jangan maksudnya itu?
Could it be that?
JOON MY SOULLLL!!!
Kok pintunya nggak kebuka?
Why won't the door open?
Oh! 10 kali! Oke!
Oh! 10 times! Okay!
JOON MY SOUL 10 times.
Eh, kayaknya bukan gitu deh.
Eh, maybe not like that.
JOON MY SOUL JOON MY SOUL JOON MY SOUL
JOON MY SOUL JOON MY SOUL JOON MY SOUL!!!
Nice.
Wanna be the biggest dreamer
全速力で未来も今も駆け抜けろ
Running full speed through the future and present
そう僕も気づいたんだ
That's right, I've realized it too
ずっと宿題忘れてた
I've forgotten my homework all this time
それはひとつの謎、謎、謎
That is a puzzle, puzzle, puzzle
「僕は誰なんだろう」
"Who am I, I wonder?"
スライディングしてすりむいた膝
Sliding and skinning my knee
痛くたってね
Even if it hurts
すぐ立ち上がらなきゃ
I have to get up right away
チャンスを逃して行く
Or the chance will slip away
分かってるさ
I know that
Big and bigger, biggest dreamer!
夢見ることがすべて始まり
Dreaming is how it all begins
それが答えだろ
That's the answer, right?
誰より遠くへ飛んでみせるよ
I'll show you I can fly further than anyone
すべての明日を貫いて
Piercing through every tomorrow
地平線まで飛んで行け
Fly all the way to the horizon
羽をもらった勇気たち
With the courage that was given wings
強く大きくなるために
In order to become strong and big
僕も走り出そう
I'll start running too
聞こえていたよ　カウントダウン
I could hear it, the countdown
ずっと前から
From a long time ago
準備はできてるさ
I'm already prepared
今すぐ始めよう
Let's start right now
ゼロに変われ
Change into zero
Big and bigger, biggest dreamer!
信じなきゃ　瞬きしてる
If you don't believe, in a blink
刹那に消えるよ
It'll vanish in an instant
心の標的逸らさず走れ
Run without looking away from your target
すべての力をぶつけよう
Let's throw all our power into it
Big and bigger, biggest dreamer!
夢見ることがすべて始まり
Dreaming is how it all begins
それが答えだろ
That's the answer, right?
誰より遠くへ飛んでみせるよ
I'll show you I can fly further than anyone
すべての明日を貫いて
Piercing through every tomorrow
BIG AND BIG AND BIGGEST DREAMER
夢見ること
Dreaming...
がすべて始まり
is where everything begins
それが答えだろう
That's the answer, isn't it?
誰より遠くへ
Further than anyone else,
飛んで見せるよ
I'll show you I can fly
すべての明日を
Every tomorrow,
貫いて
I'll pierce through them all
BIG AND BIG AND BIGGEST DREAMER
夢見ること
Dreaming...
がすべて始まり
is where everything begins
それが答えだろう
That's the answer, isn't it?
Wanna be the biggest dreamer
全速力で
At full speed,
未来も今も
both the future and the now,
駆け抜けろ
run through them
爆弾？！
A bomb?!
Buset, ini sih bener-bener udah keterlaluan.
Darn, this is really over the top.
Harusnya sekarang aku lagi 3D showcase,
I was supposed to be doing my 3D showcase now,
tapi malah nyasar, kejebak di ruangan yang ada bomnya,
but I got lost and trapped in a room with a bomb,
terus disuruh mecahin kode morse.
and I'm told to decipher Morse code.
Hari ini apes banget!
What a fabulous day!
Terus ada hape juga?
And there's a phone too?
Aku harus ngapain?
What am I supposed to do?
Telepon YAGOO terus bilang aku nyasar dan perlu bantuan?
Call YAGOO and tell him I'm lost and need help?
Wait, kayaknya aku tahu harus ngapain!
Wait, I think I know what to do!
もしもし？
Hi, hello?
Aku nyasar, kejebak, terus ada bom juga.
I'm lost and I'm trapped with a bomb.
え？
What?
Kalau kamu nggak bisa mecahin kode morse, bisa mampus aku.
I hope you can solve a Morse code or it's so over.
え？
Huh?
Garis titik garis, titik titik titik, titik dot, garis garis, garis garis garis, titik dot, garis titik garis, titik dot.
Dash-dot-dash, dot-dot-dot, dot-dash, dash-dash, dash-dash-dash, dot-dot, dash-dot-dash, dot-dash.
C... H... A...
Cepetan!
Fast!
Sunnya nau meledaak!
It's gonna explode!
Bisa ulangin lagi nggak?
Can you repeat it again?
Garis titik garis, titik titik titik, titik dash, garis garis, garis garis garis, titik dot, garis titik garis, titik dot.
Dash-dot-dash, dot-dot-dot, dot-dash, dash-dash, dash-dash-dash, dot-dot, dash-dot-dash, dot-dash.
M... O... N... ええと……
M... O... N... Um...
CHAMONって何なに？
What is CHAMON?
マジで死ぬかも…
I think I'm gonna die for real.
最後は、Y... A...
I think the last one is Y... A...
ちゃちゃもんじゃ？
CHAMONYA?
何それ？
What?
Aku nggak tahu kamu lagi ngapain, tapi semoga berhasil!
I don't know what you're doing, but good luck!
Makasih! Bye!
Thanks! Bye!
ちゃ、ちゃちゃもんじゃ……
Cha, chamonya...
ちゃちゃもんじゃ？！
Chachamonja?!
ちゃちゃもんじゃ！
Chachamonja!
I really want to be with you
I really wanna really wanna be with you
You're my love, you're my star, you're my dear
So trust me, trust me, trust me, yeah
いつでもそばにいるから
I'll always be by your side
ここに僕がいるから
Because I am right here
Trust me もう何も恐れないで
Trust me, don't be afraid of anything anymore
My dear 見えない糸で
My dear, with an invisible thread
Trust me 繋がっているから
Trust me, because we are connected
ただ感じていて この温もり
Just feel this warmth
ちゃんと聞こえている
I can hear it clearly
君の心の声
The voice of your heart
小さな不安さえ
Even the smallest anxiety
僕が包み込んであげる
I will embrace it for you
何度も伝えたい
I want to tell you over and over
君は一人じゃない
That you are not alone
変わることのない
Unchanging,
愛はきっとここにある
love is surely right here
泣いてみればいい
It's okay to cry
頼ってみればいい
It's okay to lean on me
そのすべてを受け止めると決めた
I've decided to accept all of it
I'm here どこにいたって
I'm here, no matter where you are
Call me 一つになれる
Call me, we can become one
Trust me この想い解けないから
Trust me, because this feeling won't unravel
My dear 抱えた荷物
My dear, the burden you carry
Trust me 降ろしてみればいい
Trust me, you should try setting it down
そう君のために 僕がいるんだ
Yes, I am here for your sake
Really want to be with you
Trust me, trust me, trust me, yeah
どれほどの悲しみ
How much sadness
君は隠してたの
have you been hiding?
どれほどの想いを
How many thoughts
胸に閉じ込めてきたの
have you kept locked in your chest?
痛みと引き換えに
In exchange for the pain,
手に入れた強さを
the strength you've gained
いつか優しさが
Someday, kindness
君を変えてゆけるはず
should be able to change you
奪われたって
Even if things are taken away
壊されたって
Even if things are destroyed
大事なのは自分らしくいること
What's important is staying true to yourself
I'm here たとえ世界が
I'm here, even if the world
Call me 終わるとしても
Call me, were to end
Trust me 繋いだ手 離さないから
Trust me, because I won't let go of your hand
I really wanna be with you
I really wanna, really wanna be with you
'Cause you my love, you my shine, you my dear, so
Trust me, trust me, trust me, yeah
未来へ歩き出そう
Let's start walking toward the future
そう 君のため 僕がいるんだ
Yes, I'm here for you
I'm here そばにいるから
I'm here, because I'm by your side
君に僕がいるから
Because I'm here for you
Trust me
もう何も恐れないで
Don't fear anything anymore
My dear 見えない糸で
My dear, with an invisible thread
Trust me 繋がっているから
Trust me, because we are connected
ただ感じていて この温もり
Just feel this warmth
いつまでもそばにいて forever
Stay by my side forever, forever
いつまでも離れないで never ever
Don't ever leave, never ever
君がいれば whatever you do
If I have you, whatever you do
僕に教えて whatever you say
Tell me, whatever you say
辛いことあれば すべて飲み込み
If something painful happens, I'll swallow it all
それでも無理ならば Call me, Call me
And if it's still too much, call me, call me
You're my love, you're my shine, you're my dear
世界を敵に回しても Trust me
Even if the world turns against you, Trust me
泣いてみればいい 頼ってみればいい
It's okay to cry, it's okay to rely on me
そのすべてを 受け止めると決めた
I've decided to accept all of it
I'm here どこにいたって
I'm here, no matter where you are
君とひとつになれる
I can become one with you
Trust me この思い ほどけないから
Trust me, because these feelings won't unravel
My dear 抱えきれず
My dear, if you can't carry it all
Trust me 下ろしてみればいい
Trust me, it's okay to let it down
そう 君のため 僕がいるんだ
Yes, I'm here for you
I'm here そばにいるから
I'm here, because I'm by your side
君に僕がいるから
Because I'm here for you
Trust me
もう何も恐れないで
Don't fear anything anymore
My dear 見えない糸で
My dear, with an invisible thread
Trust me 繋がっているから
Trust me, because we are connected
ただ感じていて この温もり
Just feel this warmth
With me もう離れないで
With me, don't leave anymore
Kiss me 心を開いて
Kiss me, open your heart
Feel me すべてを伝えて Yeah Yeah Yeah
Feel me, convey everything to me, yeah yeah yeah
With me 言葉はいらない
With me, words are unnecessary
Kiss me 見つめ合えばいい
Kiss me, we just need to gaze at each other
Feel me すべてを預けて Yeah Yeah Yeah
Feel me, entrust everything to me, yeah yeah yeah
Hello...?
Anybody here?
Is anyone here?
Okay, I have played enough horror games and I don't know why,
Okay, I've played enough horror games, but for some reason,
but it reminds me of something similar.
this feels really familiar.
Should I read this?
Maybe?
何が目的ですか
What is the purpose?
何でいるんですか
Why are you here?
切れてますか
Are you mad?
怒ってますか
Are you angry?
ここにいていいですか
Is it okay to be here?
戻ります
I'm going back
帰りましょうか
Shall we go home?
戻ろうか
Should we go back?
何すればいい
What should I do?
何か手伝えますか
Can I help with anything?
敵意はありますか
Is there any hostility?
何者ですか
Who are you?
どこにいますか
Where are you?
近くにいますか
Are you nearby?
出てきて
Come out
アピールしてください
Please reveal yourself
もしもし
Hello
Okay, that door looks similar to the entrance door.
That door looks like the entrance door.
Is that the exit?
Could that be the exit?
Or is that a trap?
Or is it a trap?
Well, if this is a horror game...
should I try to scream?
maybe I should try screaming?
AAAAAAAAAAAAH!
黙れ！
Shut up!
え？
Eh?
そうさ 悲しみを優しさに 自分らしさを力に
Yes, turn your sadness into kindness, your uniqueness into strength
迷いながらでもいい 歩き出して
It's okay to be lost, just start walking
もう一回
Once again
誰かの期待にずっと応えて
Always meeting someone's expectations
褒められるのが好きなのですか？
Is it being praised that you love?
なりたい自分を摺り替えても
Even if you substitute the person you want to be
笑顔はいつでも素敵ですか？
Is your smile always wonderful?
始まりだけ 夢見て起きる
Dreaming only of the beginning before waking
その先なら いつか
If it's what lies beyond, then someday
自分の腕で
with my own arms
そうだ 大事なものはいつでも
That's right, the important things are always
形のないものだけ
only those that have no form
手に入れようとして 壊していた
I broke them while trying to obtain them
形のないものだけ
Only the things with no shape,
手に入れても なくしても
whether I obtain them or lose them,
気づかぬまま
I remain unaware.
そうさ
That's right,
悲しみを優しさに
turn sadness into kindness,
自分らしさを力に
and your uniqueness into strength.
迷いながらでもいい
It's okay to be lost,
歩き出して
just start walking.
もう一回
One more time!
ように
...so it won't fade away.
Why does everything feel so real?
Am I real?
Can you even feel my existence?
Is this what Deja vu looks like?
All these memories mean the world to me.
Thank you for walking this journey with me.
Let's make more! :3 Like! Comments! Share! Subscribe!